<application>
  <component name="AppStorage">
    <histories>
      <item value="distinct User Map" />
      <item value="distinct" />
      <item value="SMTP Address Failed Exception" />
      <item value="zhenyinxiang" />
      <item value="Connection refused: connect" />
      <item value="create Mime Message" />
      <item value="Dear Beneficiary,     I hope that this correspondence is received with the urgency and expediency required.It has come to the notice of the Board of Trustees of the Federal Reserve Bank here in Washington, D.C. that your present inheritance claims application being handled by the Remitting Bank in Nigeria is experiencing some man made irregularities. To this effect, it has become necessary for the Board of Trustees to assign trained Fund Transfer Specialists from the United States to resolve and regularize your fund release with immediate effect.     We at Deborah L. Hayes &amp; Corporate Affairs have been duly consulted by the FRB Board of Trustees. We have been fully informed about how the staffs of the remitting bank has been taking advantage of you by telling you to pay unnecessarily exorbitant charges which will only make your fund payment a long drawn out process.     Due to this development, we have been assigned to step into the immediate processing of your fund transfer to enable your funds to be transferred to you within the shortest possible time. To implement this, you are to get back to us immediately without needing to pay all the huge sums of monies that are being demanded from you by the previous handlers at the remitting bank.     All processes to have your funds paid to you immediately through the CBN's Liaison Remittance Office in New York have been initiated to cut out unnecessary costs.   You are advised to treat this communication with the urgency and seriousness required as the Board of Trustees of the Federal Reserve Bank has mandated us to resolve this fund payment within the next three working days independent of the office of the Remitting Bank in Africa.     Furthermore,you are hereby advised to pay no further fees or charges to the Remitting Bank in Nigeria as they shall no longer be handling your payment process.     We shall await your immediate correspondence with your direct telephone numbers to my private email address at (deborahhayes11111@gmail.com) for re-confirmation so that we may conclude your payment immediately.     Yours Sincerely,       Deborah L. Hayes Senior Vice President of Corporate Affairs " />
      <item value="Returns a {@code Collector} implementing a &quot;group by&quot; operation on * input elements of type {@code T}, grouping elements according to a * classification function, and returning the results in a {@code Map}." />
      <item value="ELIFECYCLE" />
      <item value="divide" />
      <item value="Bill Date" />
      <item value="Bill Remind" />
      <item value="Bill Remind Date" />
      <item value="Stop Service Remind" />
      <item value="Late Fee Remind" />
      <item value="new bill_25 th" />
      <item value="remind" />
      <item value="remind_20 th" />
      <item value="late fee_1 st" />
      <item value="stop service_6 th" />
      <item value="Invoice No" />
      <item value=" Permission denied " />
      <item value="element cannot be mapped to a null key" />
      <item value="ambiguous" />
      <item value="Lock wait timeout exceeded; try restarting transaction; nested exception is com.mysql.jdbc.exceptions.jdbc4.MySQLTransactionRollbackException: Lock wait timeout exceeded; try restarting transaction" />
      <item value="try restarting transaction" />
      <item value="Lock wait timeout exceeded" />
      <item value="is Rju Floor" />
      <item value="subtract" />
      <item value="减" />
      <item value="除" />
      <item value="Returns the minimum of this {@code BigDecimal} and" />
      <item value="get Fragment In Days" />
      <item value="rent Free Amt Total" />
      <item value="Returns a stream consisting of the distinct elements" />
      <item value="Ratio" />
      <item value="拒绝" />
      <item value="refuse" />
      <item value="reject" />
      <item value="Test Quartz Job" />
      <item value="Error:java: Annotation processing is not supported for module cycles. Please ensure that all modules from cycle [server-next,next-custom-server] are excluded from annotation processing" />
      <item value="X" />
      <item value="II" />
      <item value="I" />
      <item value="status" />
      <item value="take" />
      <item value="take Up" />
      <item value="customer" />
      <item value="source" />
      <item value="来源" />
    </histories>
    <option name="languageScores">
      <map>
        <entry key="CHINESE" value="4377" />
        <entry key="ENGLISH" value="4464" />
        <entry key="FRENCH" value="46" />
        <entry key="PORTUGUESE" value="31" />
        <entry key="SPANISH" value="10" />
      </map>
    </option>
  </component>
  <component name="Settings">
    <option name="foldOriginal" value="true" />
    <option name="ignoreRegExp" value="" />
    <option name="translator" value="ai.youdao" />
    <option name="youdaoTranslateSettings">
      <youdao-translate>
        <option name="appId" value="790d8c17d9b6123c" />
        <option name="appKeyConfigured" value="true" />
      </youdao-translate>
    </option>
  </component>
</application>